(Raj:)Wow.
(Leonard:)No, it's great.
- Also, uh, mint-in-box.
- Mm.
(Penny:)- And I got you a Transporter too!
- Awesome!
(Sheldon:)Look, it was actually designed
for my vintage Mr. Spock action figure.
(Penny:)Oh, that's great.
Open it and put him in there.
- Open it?
- No, good Lord, no.
Why? They're just toys.
- Collectibles.
- They're mint-in-box.
Can't we open one up and take a look?
- Aah!
- No, don't!
(Leonard:)Once you open the box, it loses its value.
(Penny:)Yeah, yeah. My mom gave me
the same lecture about my virginity.
(Penny:)Gotta tell you, it was a lot more fun
taking it out and playing with it.
(Bernadette:)You sure you want us here
when you meet this woman?
Oh, yes. Ln my cuIture, it's expected to
have a chaperone to oversee a first date.